page1profit.com 2011-03-16

# GYH Business Services – Terms and Conditions & Privacy Policy

Terms and Conditions 

We are also so confident you will love our services, by placing your order today you will also be enrolled in our monthly Page1Profit Membership Program at a monthly rate of $74.95.

With this service you will never again have to worry if your site is being marketed. We will conveniently bill your card on file the special low monthly price of $74.95 to cover the marketing services for that month. If you decide not to participate any longer in our membership program, simply contact us by phone or email. Please note: All cancelled members will receive an email notification confirming cancellation. You can call us at 1-800-208-6407 or send an email to support@page1profit.com. Communication via email is the quickest and most reliable method in canceling your membership.

Returns/Refunds Policy

Please note: There are no refunds for monthly services already charged and begun.

100% Satisfaction Guaranteed

If you are not satisfied with the initial trial for whatever reason, please let us know and we would be happy to un-enroll you from our program.

Changes to Terms and Conditions

We reserve the right to make any changes necessary to the terms and conditions at any time without prior notification.

**Types of Information We Collect:**

Public Information – You may visit the web site anonymously. During your visit, we may collect information that is not personally identifiable such as your IP address, site usage, purchase behavior, browser type, browser activity, and browser settings. 

Private Information – We may collect information about you to provide you with the services that you request. The information we collect may include but is not limited to name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card or other information. 

**How the Collected Information is Used:**   

Public Information – We may use anonymous information that we collect about your visit to enhance the operation of the website. For example, we use anonymous information to make the website more navigable or to remember what is contained in your shopping cart or history. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us to better understand our site visitors and to help us tailor the website function accordingly. 

Private Information – We use the personal data you submit to provide you with the services you request. For example, we may require you to submit personal information to fulfill your order, complete registration on the website, or send you information about our products. We may use this information to personalize your site experience. We may also share your information with third parties to deliver content or product offerings to you that we believe are of interest to you. In the event that a portion or all of the our interest in the website are sold or leased, all personal information would be transferred to the acquiring or leasing party. We may share your personal information as may be required by law or court order or with a law-enforcement or other government agency in connection with a criminal investigation, fraud prevention or other legal action if we reasonably believe it is necessary to do so to protect us, our customers or the public. 

We also may disclose your personal information or financial information to our subsidiary and parent companies and businesses, and other affiliated legal entities and businesses with whom we are under common corporate control. Whenever personal information or financial information is disclosed under this paragraph we may also disclose your demographic information, on a non-anonymous basis. All of our parent, subsidiary and affiliated legal entities and businesses that receive your personal information, financial information, or non-anonymous demographic information from us will comply with the terms of this privacy policy with respect to their use and disclosure of such information. 

To operate the site, including processing your transactions and supporting your activities on the site, we may share your personal information with our agents, representatives, contractors and service providers so they can provide us with support services such as authorization of credit card transactions, email origination, receipt or support services, customer relationship management services, order fulfillment and sweepstakes and promotional fulfillment. By purchasing, or registering or making reservations for, products or services offered or sponsored by third parties on the site, or electing to receive communications (such as emails or magazine subscriptions) or electing to participate in contests, sweepstakes or other programs (such as discount or rewards programs), offered or sponsored by third parties on the site, you consent to our providing your personal information to those third parties. Those third parties may use your personal information in accordance with their own privacy policies. You will need to contact those third parties to instruct them directly regarding your preferences for the use of your personal information by them. Additionally, you agree that we may use and disclose all such information so submitted to such third parties in the same manner in which we are entitled to use and disclose any other information you submit to us. 

To enhance your experience as a site member, we send out message notifications, newsletters and site announcements, and from time to time third party offers from companies that we feel may have something that will benefit you. Our site provides you with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving different types of communications (except system communications, or communications required for account maintenance), and each email that we send out has a method for opting-out located at the bottom of the message. 

**Opt-Out and CAN-SPAM Act**   

When you become a Member, you will automatically be registered to receive promotional offers and updates, via e-mails, from us and from the Network sites and other associated e-mail brands. 

Additionally, when you become a Member, you will be provided with the opportunity to receive promotional offers, via e-mails, from partners of ours. While some of these opportunities will only be sent to you if you expressly request them, others may be sent to you unless you elect not to receive them. Accordingly, please review these offers carefully. 

Members may, at any time, choose not to receive promotional e-mails from www.page1profit.com, the network sites or partners of ours by following the "unsubscribe" instructions in the applicable e-mail. Notwithstanding the foregoing, we may continue to contact Members for the purpose of communicating information about their membership with us to Members, or similar information relating to us, the site or your membership, as well as to facilitate, complete or confirm any transaction that Members’ enter into or in response to or fulfillment of Members’ inquiries or requests. 

Note that unsubscribing from one e-mail list does not automatically unsubscribe you from any other e-mail list that you may be on. Please read the e-mail carefully to find out which list you are unsubscribing from. 

Unless otherwise noted, the site, www.page1profit.com e-mails and the content available in connection therewith, are neither intended for, nor directed to, children under the age of 18. Except as otherwise noted, if we learn that a person who is a Member is under the age of 18, we will promptly terminate that individual’s membership.

Changes to our Privacy Policy

www.Page1Profit.com may, from time to time, amend this Policy, in whole or part, in its sole discretion. Any changes to this Policy will be effective immediately upon the posting of the revised policy on the Site

Contact us with your questions or suggestions

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy, please contact our Customer Care Department at support@page1profit.com

Contact Us:

Contact us with your questions or suggestions at [support@page1profit.com](mailto:support@page1profit.com)
